export const DataLatGramMud = [
    //1
    {
        question: 'I _____ a book every day.',
        options: [
            "read",
            "reads",
            "am reading",
            "have read",
        ],
        answer: 0,
    },
    // 2
    {
        question: 'She _____ to school by bus.',
        options: [
            'go',
            'goes',
            'went',
            'going',
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    // 3
    {
        question: 'They _____ pizza on Fridays.',
        options: [
            "like",
            "likes",
            "liking",
            "are liking",
        ],
        answer: 0,
    },
    // 4
    {
        question: 'He _____ not play tennis.',
        options: [
            "do",
            "is",
            "does",
            "are",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    // 5
    {
        question: 'We _____ happy today.',
        options: [
            "Is",
            "are",
            "am",
            "be",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    // 6
    {
        question: 'The cat _____ on the mat.',
        options: [
            "sit",
            "sits",
            "sitting",
            "is sitting",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    // 7
    {
        question: 'She _____ a new dress yesterday.',
        options: [
            "buy",
            "buys",
            "bought",
            "buying",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    // 8
    {
        question: 'They _____ to the movies last night.',
        options: [
            "go",
            "goes",
            "went",
            "going",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    // 9
    {
        question: 'He _____ speak Spanish.',
        options: [
            "can",
            "will",
            "may",
            "could",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    // 10
    {
        question: 'We _____ eat ice cream.',
        options: [
            "want",
            "wants",
            "wanting",
            "are wanting"
        ],
        answer: 0,
    },
]